A Guide to the Russell Sage Foundation records, Office of the President, Eric Wanner papers, Record Group 1 FA764
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Working papers, 1962-2010; 1; 5.1 Cubic Feet 6 letter boxes, 1 half-letter box, 2 record storage boxes
  - 160 - Gender Differences in Pay, 2000 May; Blau, Francine D.; Kahn, Lawrence M. (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 161 - Can Boosting Minority Car-Ownership Rates Narrow Inter-Racial Employment Gaps?, 2000 June; Stoll, Michael A.; Raphael, Steven (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 162 - Political Patronage, Bureaucracy and Corruption in Postwar Italy, 2000 September; Golden, Miriam A. (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 163 - Cooption and Repression in the Soviet Union, 2000 September; Gershenson, Dmitry; Grossman, Herschel (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 164 - Beyond the digital divide, 2000 November; Attewell, Paul A. (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 165 - Decisiveness and the Viability of Anarchy, 2000 November; Grossman, Herschel; Kim, Minseong; Mendoza, Juan (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 166 - "Make Us King": Anarchy, Predation, and the State, 2000 November; Grossman, Herschel (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 167 - The Development of Germany's Banking System, 1800-1914, 2000 November; Guinnane, Timothy W. (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 168 - Veto Players and Referendums Around the World, 2000 November; Hug, Simon; Tsebelis, George (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 169 - Dismantling the Leviathan: Political Theory and Membership, 2000 November; Benhabib, Seyla (Box 7, Folder 34)
    Philosophy
  - 170 - The creation of effective property rights, 2000 December; Grossman, Herschel (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 171 - Annexation or Conquest? The Economics of Empire Building, 2001 January; Grossman, Herschel; Mendoza, Juan (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 172 - Education Inequality, 2001 March; Azuma, Yoshiaki; Grossman, Herschel (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 173 - Educational Policy: Egalitarian or Elitist?, 2001 March; Grossman, Herschel; Kim, Minseong (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 174 - Veto Players and the Structure of Budgets in Advanced Industrialized Countries, 2001 March; Tsebelis, George; Chang, Eric (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 175 - Investors and Pirates: Creative and Intellectual Property Rights, 2001 April; Grossman, Herschel (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 176 - Incentives, Information, and Welfare: England's New Poor Law and the Workhouse Test, 2001 May; Besley, Timothy; Coate, Stephen; Guinnane, Timothy W. (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 177 - The Mellon Literacy Project: What does it teach us about educational research, practice, and sustainability?, 2001 June; Ginsburg, Herbert (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 178 - The Next Generation: Russian Jewish Young Adults in Contemporary New York, 2001 June; Kasinitz, Philip, 1957-; Zelzer-Zubida, Aviva; Simakhodskaya, Zoya (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 179 - Predicting failure but failing to predict: a sociology of knowledge of credit rating in post-bellum America, 2001 June; Carruthers, Bruce G.; Cohen, Barry (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 180 - The legacy of apartheid: racial differences in the legitimacy of democratic institutions and processes in the new South Africa, 2001 November; Gibson, James L. (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 181 - Race and support for the criminal justice system: a matter of asymmetry, 2001 December; Pena, Yesilernis L.; Federico, Christopher; Sidanius, Jim (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - 182 - The supreme court and the U.S. presidential election of 2000: wounds, self-inflicted or otherwise?, 2002 January; Gibson, James L. (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - 183 - Racism, ideology, and affirmative acion, revisted: the antecedents and consequences of 'principled objections' to affirmative action, 2001 December; Federico, Christopher; Sidanius, Jim (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - 184 - Sophistication and the antecedents of Whites' racial-policy attitudes: racism, ideology, and affirmative action in America, 2001 December; Federico, Christopher; Sidanius, Jim (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - 185 - Truth, justice, and reconciliation: judging the fairness of Amnesty in South Africa, 2002 February; Gibson, James L. (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - 186 - Social dominance orientation, authoritarianism, religious identification and support for terrorism in the Middle East, 2002 April; Henry, PJ; Sidanius, Jim; Levin, Shana; Pratto, Felicia (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - 187 - Why do they hate us so? The clash of civilizations or the politics of dominance?, 2002 April; Sidanius, Jim; Henry, PJ; Pratto, Felicia; Levin, Shana (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - 188 - The gendered nature of family structure and group-based anti-egalitarianism: A cross-national analysis, 2002 April; Pena, Yesilernis L.; Federico, Christopher; Sidanius, Jim (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - 189 - Truth, reconciliation, and the creation of a human rights culture in South Africa: an investigation of the effectiveness of the truth and reconciliation process, 2002 April; Gibson, James L. (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - 190 - Cuban exceptionalism: group based hierarchy and the dynamics of patriotism in Puerto Rico, the Dominican Republic, and China, 2002 May; Sawyer, Mark Q.; Pena, Yesilernis L.; Sidanius, Jim (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - 191 - The Effects of ingroup and outgroup friendships on ethnic attitudes in college: a longitudinal study, 2002 May; Levin, Shana; Sidanius, Jim; van Laar, Colette (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - 192 - In search of a viable common ingroup identity: a social dominance perspective, 2002 June; Sidanius, Jim; van Laar, Colette; Levin, Shana; Sinclair, Stacey (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - 193 - Social hierarchy maintenance and the allocation of social roles: a social dominance perspective, 2002 June; Sidanius, Jim; van Laar, Colette; Levin, Shana; Sinclair, Stacey (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - 194 - Ethnic enclaves on the college campus: the good, the bad, and the ugly, 2002 July; Sidanius, Jim; van Laar, Colette; Levin, Shana; Sinclair, Stacey (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - 195 - Tools of the trade: the socio-technology of arbitrage in a Wall Street trading room, 2002 October; Beunza, Daniel; Stark, David (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - 196 - Bankruptcy "reform" in Congress: creditors, committees, ideology, and floor voting in the legislative process, 2002 October; Nunez, Stephen; Rosenthal, Howard (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - 197 - Government instability with perfect spatial voting: France 1946-1958, 2002 October; Rosenthal, Howard; Voeten, Erik (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - 198 - Narrative Nuances on Good and Bad Deaths: Internists' Tales from High-technology Work Places, 2002 November; DelVecchio Good, Mary-Jo; Gadmer, Nina M.; Ruopp, Patricia; Lakoma, Matthew; Sullivan, Amy M.; Arnold, Robert M.; Block, Susan D. (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - 199 - The culture of medicine and racial, ethnic, and class disparities in health care, 2002 December; DelVecchio Good, Mary-Jo; Good, Byron; Becker, Anne E. (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - 200 - Trade expansion and contract enforcement, 2003 January; Dixit, Avinash (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - 201 - Political polarization and income inequality, 2003 February; McCarty, Nolan; Poole, Keith T.; Rosenthal, Howard (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - 202 - Immigration and wealth inequality in the U.S., 2003 February; Hao, Lingxin (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - 203 - The Retreat of multiculturalism in the liberal state, 2003 January; Joppke, Christian (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - 204 - Citizenship between de- and re-ethnicization, 2003 March; Joppke, Christian (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - 205 - The Resilience of nondiscriminatory immigration policies: evidence from the United States and Australia, 2003 April; Joppke, Christian (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - 206 - Social theory, modernity, and the three waves of historical sociology, 2003 April; Adams, Julia; Clemens, Elisabeth S.; Orloff, Ann Shola (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - 207 - Welfare reform and teenage pregnancy, childbirth, and school dropout, 2003 April; Hao, Lingxin; Cherlin, Andrew J. (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - 208 - The rule of the father: patriarchy and patrimonialism in early modern Europe, 2003 July; Adams, Julia (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - 209 - The contribution of social support to the economic status and daily coping of former and current welfare recipients, 2003 March; Danziger, Sandra (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - 210 - The medical imaginary and biotechnical embrace subjective experiences of clincal scientists and patients, 2003 June; DelVecchio Good, Mary-Jo (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - 211 - The rise of markets in the western world: a global comparison, 2003 May; Shiue, Carol (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - 212 - Employment duration of African-American and White welfare recipients and the role of persistent health and mental health problems, 2003 July; Corcoran, Mary E.; Danziger, Sandra; Tolman, Richard (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - 213 - A desk on the 20th floor; survival and sense making in a trading room, 2003 November; Beunza, Daniel; Stark, David (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - 214 - Wage inequality, earnings inequality and poverty in the US over the last quarter of the twentieth century, 2004 May; Gottschalk, Peter; Danziger, Sheldon (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - 215 - Connecting race, gender, and class identities through the study of Black lesbian-headed families, 2005 February; Moore, Mignon R. (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - 216 - Job satisfaction and co-worker wages: status or signal?, 2007 September; Clark, Andrew E.; Westergard-Nielsen, Niels; Kristensen, Nicolai (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - 217 - Great Expectations: Law, Employment Contracts, and Labor Market Performance, 2010 October; MacLeod, W. Bentley (Box 9, Folder 42)